http://www.ycp.edu/privacy-statement/

Health & Wellness
Spartan Spirit!
Graduate Studies Catalog
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
Adult-Gerontology Nurse Practitioner Primary Care
Curriculum
Graduate Studies Catalog
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
Adult-Gerontology Post Master's Certificate
Curriculum
Graduate Studies Catalog
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
Adult-Gerontology Clinical Nurse Specialist
Curriculum - Education Focus
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
Nurse Educator
Curriculum
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
Psychiatric Mental Health Nurse Practitioner
Doctor of Nursing Practice
DNP Nurse Anesthetist
Curriculum
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
DNP Post Master's
Curriculum
Graduate Student Handbook (PDF)
Theatre Education Endorsement
Financial Planning (Certificate)
Programs
English (Literary and Textual Studies)
Medical Humanities
Music (B.A.)
Performance Ensembles
Music B.S. (With Studies in Music Industry and Recording Technology)
Spanish Business
Theatre (B.A.)
Co-op Requirements
Dr. Donald E. and Lois J. Myers School of Nursing and Health Professions
Our Alumni
Nursing Student Handbook (PDF)
York College Privacy Statement
York College of Pennsylvania (YCP) is committed to protecting your privacy and security. Security procedures are continually updated and improved. This privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways our websites collect information, the uses of this information and the way this information is protected.
YCP does not collect your personal information when you visit one of our websites unless you choose to provide that information to us. By visiting YCP websites you consent to the collection and use of information as described in this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time without advance notice.
Personal Information
YCP collects personal information when you submit a form that contains your personal information in order to make a request of or to report something to us. Personal information may include but is not limited to:
Name
Address
Telephone Number
Email address
YCP does not share your personal information submitted to us with external vendors. We may release your information when required or allowed to do so by federal, state, or local regulations.
For various purposes, such as applying, requesting college information, or scheduling a visit, we link to authorized third-party vendor partners such as Technolutions / Slate. The vendor partners collect your personal information on their websites to carry out the desired services.
Non-Personal Information
Non-personal information is collected automatically by our web servers and by our authorized third party vendors through the use of electronic tools like cookies and pixel tags. Examples of non-personal information that we collect includes but is not limited to:
The date and time you visit our website.
The pages, files, documents and links that you visit.
The Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the website you visited before coming to our website and the URL of the website you visit after leaving our website.
The type of browser you are using.
Your Internet Protocol (IP) address.
Cookies
In addition to information we collect automatically we and our authorized third-party vendors use cookies, which are small text files sent to your browser and stored on your computer when you visit our websites and partner websites. These cookies do not collect personal information. Cookies are used to track visitor usage patterns, traffic trends and other information from visits in order to help us improve and deliver effective, robust website service.
We use cookies to store personal preferences our visitors voluntarily select when visiting My York Experience. The preferences stored on your computer present personalized content on your return visits to our website.
We may use authorized third-party vendors such as Hobsons to carry out services such as applying to YCP, sending you information about YCP that you requested or scheduling a visit to YCP. These vendors may use cookies to support their services when you return to our website. Our privacy policy does not apply to any information these vendors may have collected about your visit on their websites.
We may use authorized third-party vendors such as Google Analytics and SiteImprove to track visitor interactions with our website to help us understand how visitors use or engage with our website and to help us improve and deliver effective, robust website service. We do not combine the information collected by these services with any personal information.
We may use authorized third-party vendors such as SumoMe to allow visitors to share content from our website with others on social media platforms. These vendors may use cookies to collect non-personal information via the Share buttons on our website to monitor traffic and usage patterns to help us deliver effective, robust website service.
We may use authorized third-party vendors such as AdRoll and Facebook to display ads featuring YCP on other websites. These vendors may use cookies to display these ads based on information collected from your visit to our website. Our privacy policy does not apply to any information these vendors may have collected about your visit.
We may embed social media content from Twitter, Facebook and other social media services. These embedded social media plug-ins use cookies to monitor traffic from our website to theirs and to support visitors logging in to the respective social media accounts if the visitor interacts with the embedded social media content while visiting our website.
You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website that you visit. If you turn off cookies in your browser when you visit our website, you will eliminate only the ability to save preferences from My York Experience. Otherwise, your experience on our website will not be affected.
We work with the following vendors regularly or on a periodic basis. Please visit the websites below to view their privacy policies. New vendors that we work with and vendors that we no longer work with will be added and removed without notice.
http://www.technosolutions.com/privacy-policy.htmlhttps://privacy.google.com/https://siteimprove.com/en/privacy/privacy-policy/https://twitter.com/en/privacyhttps://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy/
-
Follow us on Twitter
Follow us on Instagram
Tweets by @yorkcollegepa
Follow us on Instagram
New to YCP? Let us help you find your path.
Toggle
Dismiss
Welcome Back! View Your York Experience!
Dismiss
Explore the information on our site that matters to you most.
Choose My York Experience
Close
My York Experience
Tell us your interests and jump right to the stuff that matters most to you.
1What best describes you?
I am ...
2What interests you?
I have no idea!
3What would you like to know about life at York?
